We all know that cleaning our teeth is important, right?
我们都知道刷牙很重要，对吧？
Because, if you don’t clean them and things go wrong, they can cause you a lot of pain and discomfort.
因为如果不刷牙，牙齿出了问题，会给你带来极大的疼痛和不适。
We’re taught from a young age how to clean our teeth, but the question is – do we all clean our teeth in the same way?
我们从小就被教导如何刷牙，但问题是——每个人的刷牙方式都一样吗？
Is there a specific time, technique, or duration you should be incorporating into your dental routine?
在日常口腔护理中，是否需要遵循特定的时间、方法或是时长呢？
When our milk teeth first appear in our infant years, we are shown, often by our parents, how to clean them – a ritual normally accompanied by some kind of catchy song.
婴幼儿时期，乳牙刚长出来时，通常是父母手把手教我们刷牙——这个过程还常常伴着一首朗朗上口的儿歌。
As we mature, our baby teeth drop out, replaced by adult teeth.
随着我们长大成人，乳牙脱落，恒牙取而代之。
And soon it’s from trips to the dentists that we get more advice.
之后，我们从牙医那里得到更多关于刷牙的建议。
And that’s the issue – when trying to discover the best way to brush your teeth, it feels like there are so many different tips and tricks.
但问题也随之而来：当我们想找到最佳刷牙方式时，总会发现各种各样的技巧和窍门。
University College London (UCL) analysed 66 sources of toothbrushing advice from around the world.
伦敦大学学院分析了来自全球的66份刷牙建议资料。
The most commonly recommended techniques incorporated circular movements and horizontal brush strokes.
其中最常被推荐的刷牙方式是画圈和水平横刷。
However, there were some deviations. The angle of the brush, use of vertical movements and rigorous scrubbing were all variations on brushing advice.
不过，也存在一些不同的说法，牙刷的倾斜角度、竖刷的方式以及用力刷洗，这些都是刷牙建议中的不同版本。
And it seems that not one single technique is the standard method – so, if that’s the case, how do we know if we’re doing it right?
看起来并没有哪一种方法是唯一的标准方式——既然如此，我们怎么判断自己的刷牙方式是否正确呢？
Well – there is some standard advice.
其实还是有一些标准建议的。
It seems that brushing for between two to three minutes, two or three times a day, is the best course of action.
每天刷牙两到三次，每次持续两到三分钟，这种做法是最稳妥的。
And if you’re one of these people who think it’s wise to brush straight after sugary foods to prevent decay, think again.
如果你觉得吃完甜食后立刻刷牙能预防蛀牙，那可就错了。
Apparently, bacteria weaken the enamel almost immediately upon eating, so it’s wiser to wait for an hour or so before brushing.
很明显，吃完东西后，口腔内的细菌会迅速侵蚀牙釉质，所以最好等一个小时左右再刷牙。
So, while there is not one standardised technique, most dentists recommend a combination of horizontal and circular movements, lasting for between two to three minutes, two or three times a day.
因此，尽管没有统一的标准刷牙方法，但大多数牙医都建议结合水平横刷和画圈刷的方式，每天刷两到三次，每次两到三分钟。
Do that, and you might not need too many trips to the dentist.
坚持这样做，你去看牙医的次数或许就能少很多了。